bigmoneyarcade.com 2019-05-04

# Free Online Privacy for Games - Play Privacy for Games

* * *

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Bigmoneyarcade.com, an online flash game arcade and real-time multiplayer games entertainment portal. As a responsible company, the safety of your personal information shared to us and the protection of it from unauthorized disclosure to others, is one of our highest priorities. This privacy policy will tell you how your data are collected and used. Please read this privacy policy carefully.

Using the service means that you have the consent to the collection and use of your potential information as discussed in this privacy policy. This policy may be updated from time to time. Notice will not be posted in the forum when an update is made; It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy from time to time and if you find any of it unacceptable, you must leave the site and discontinue the use of the service and the site. Your continued use of Bigmoneyarced.com services after a change or update has been made to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change or update. 

## Collection of Data

Once you have access on our site or applications using your Bigmoneyarcade.com member account we will gather information that you provided on your profile such as name, gender, age range and e-mail address.

In game actions are also recorded. Any actions you perform with other players are considered public and your own discretion. Since all our games are played on Bigmoneyarcade.com, it is your responsibility to read and accept our posted Terms of Use.

Finally we collect information about the use of our service including information such as internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages & URLs and the date and time you use our service.

## How We Use Your Information

Personalizing your game visits and experience is one of the few things in which we use your information. We also use your personal information to manage your registration and send you news letters or other information about us.

We do not sell, share nor rent your personal information or email address. Your email address won't be shared ever! 

The information you submit to us also help us in displaying targeted advertisements for example; advertisements that are designed according to age group, the location of a user, etc. However we do not provide that information to the advertisers whenever you view an advertisement.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that a website transfers to your computer and recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user. A cookie will contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, contains certain information about your sessions or use of the service.

These cookies help us recognize you as you return to our website. These help us improve our services for cookies help us compile anonymous, collective statistics for us to analyze how users use our site, though you are not identified personally in this way.

## Third-Party Advertising Companies

We use third-party companies to serve advertisements on our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Cookies and web beacons are associated with the advertisements to enable the advertiser to track the number of anonymous respondents to the campaign.

Bigmoneyarcade.com does not provide personal information to these third-parties. We do not have access to cookies that come with these advertisements. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, or to opt-out of thsese advertisments, go to [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

## DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

## Security

We have employed precautions and technical measures to secure your information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, or disclosure. 

## Trademarks

Bigmoneyarcade.com Logo, game logo and other marks specified on this website are registered trademarks of Bigmoneyarcade.com. All games included on Bigmoneyarcade.com are the trademarks of their respective owners/publishers/developers.
